JULIÁN PÉREZ

Software engineer and Entrepreneur

julianperez.me jcpmmx @ [LinkedIn, GitHub, Gmail] +57 301 4315072 • Cali, Colombia

"Easy-going, jack of all trades, go-to guy that gets things done", as described by many.

Software engineer (BE-CS 2009) craving for disruptive software experiences that actually solve problems, learning every day and working hard to be a better person and entrepreneur.

With more than a decade of experience (7 years working remotely and abroad) helping startups, digital agencies, contract clients from around the world and enterprises in Colombia.

Skills Python; Web apps development (Django, Flask); APIs (REST, GraphQL)

Interests Startups and Entrepreneurship; Machine Learning; Data Science

EXPERIENCE

Sr. Back-end engineer at ShipHero	Remote • Jan 2019 - Mar 2020
Lead Engineer at Litimetrics	Remote • May-Dec 2018
Sr. Back-end engineer at WayUp	Remote • Jan-Apr 2018
Technical lead and Back-end developer at Mozio	Remote • Jun 2014 - Sep 2017
Full-stack web developer at ZehnerGroup	Remote • Apr 2013 - May 2014
Python/Django consultant on Upwork	Remote • Aug 2012 - Apr 2013
Cofounder/CTO of my 1st startup endeavor: Trappt	Cali, CO • Mar-Aug 2012
.NET/Oracle developer at Banco de Occidente	Cali, CO • Nov 2010 - Mar 2012
.NET/POS for .NET developer at Siesa	Cali, CO • Nov 2009 - Nov 2010

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Engineering, Computer Science Universidad del Valle, Cali, Colombia • 2009

Be so good they can't ignore you Steve Martin, according to the Internet

Last update: Feb 7, 2019